myfreefarm.com 2014-02-10

# Data Privacy Statement

This is the data privacy statement of upjers GmbH & Co. KG, Hafenstrasse 13, 96052 Bamberg, Germany. It is valid for all websites and games run by upjers. In order to be able to use the websites and games run by upjers, all users need to agree to the use of their data described below. This consent may be revoked at any time, effective immediately and indefinitely. In this case, neither websites nor games may be used.

The following includes an explanation of the most important terms, in order to facilitate an understanding of this data privacy statement.

## Glossary

_What is personal data?_  
Personal data is data allowing the user to be identified. This includes, for instance, the real name, email address, telephone number, address or credit card information of the user.

 _What is user data?_  
User data is data upjers collects from their users, processes and saves when the user visits or uses websites and games run by upjers. User data in particular includes attributes to identify the user (such as the domain name and/or the IP address of the computer the user uses to connect to upjers sites or services).

 _What are IP addresses?_  
IP addresses serve to identify machines that are connected to the internet. Each computer that is connected to the internet can be allocated a certain IP address, that is, a specific combination of numbers.

 _What is a cookie?_  
A cookie is a small text file that transmitted by the websites and games of upjers - as well as by many other websites - to the cookie file of the user's browser. The cookie is saved on the user's hard drive by the user's browser, allowing the websites and games to recognize the user on his or her next visit. A cookie contains, among other data, the domain name the cookie is from, the "operating time" of this cookie and a value, generally a specific number that has been created randomly. Cookies cannot be used to identify the user. Users can use all upjers web pages and games without cookies, if the browser is set to automatically decline them. Cookies already saved on the computer can be manually removed by the user. upjers informs its users that it may not be possible to fully utilize its games and websites without using cookies.

## § 1 Collecting, Processing and Saving Personal Data

upjers collects, processes and saves personal data that the user has willingly passed on in electronic or other forms of communication (such as in forms or otherwise on upjers websites and games). This includes data that the user confides to other users, such as by communicating with them via upjers games and sites. Certain information such as communication between users is also visible to other users of upjers websites and games.

In order to register to use upjers games, users must submit certain personal information. This includes, for instance, email addresses. If users want to make use of additional offers inside the games, upjers may need further information, such as their bank account and/or credit card details.

Here a few examples of the data that upjers saves:

If a user registers on a game run by upjers, upjers automatically saves the domain name and/or the IP address of the computer the user uses to contact upjers.

upjers saves the email address of the user, if the user has transmitted this to upjers.

## § 2 Use of Personal Data

upjers collects, processes and saves users' personal data only inasmuch as upjers thinks this is necessary for reasonable legal business purposes. upjers collects, processes and saves this user data, in order to allow the users a better use and understanding of their websites and games and to be able to offer them better service. That means that upjers, for instance, won't just be able to use the saved data to directly carry out the user contract including all its possible forms of use (such as using the games, participating in services connected to games, use of customer support), but also to detect malfunctions or misuse of upjers ' websites and games.

upjers may use the email addresses submitted by users to send newsletters and information about this game. Users may of course always withdraw their consent in writing (for instance via email), without incurring any costs, apart from those of sending in the revocation. The user can decline to receive further info-messages and newsletters sent by upjers by sending a revocation.

upjers may pass on user data to service providers charged with collecting payments, inasmuch as this is necessary to calculate the payment and to charge the user. upjers furthermore may offer user data to third-parties if upjers has commissioned them to recover debts, inasmuch as such data is necessary to claim those debts. upjers will inform the user about the name of these third-parties upon request. In case upjers cooperates with third-parties to offer their services, upjers will ensure that they adhere to the applicable data security laws and offer ample data protection.

## § 3 Change or Deletion of Personal Data

Users may change their personal data at any time (such as by updating or correcting them) or delete their data entirely. If a user wants upjers to change his/her personal data or stops using his/her personal data, the user may contact upjers via datenschutzbeauftragter@upjers.com. upjers will change or delete this user data as quickly as possible. Due to technical or organizational conditions it might be possible that some measures will still need to be carried out even after the demand of deletion, should these already have begun but haven't been completed after the user has informed upjers of his/her wish to be deleted.

## § 4 Separate Notes

**1\. Use of the Scalabe Central Measurement Method**

Upjers uses the "Scalable Central Measurement Method / Skalierbares Zentrales Messverfahren" (SZM) for several of its websites (so far My Free Farm, Molehill Empire, Kapi Hospital and Upologus) of [INFOnline](https://www.infonline.de/) to determine statistical parameters in the scope of Upjers' services. In doing so, anonymous measures are collected. For the recognition of computer systems, the SZM audience measurement uses alternatively either a cookie with the identifier "ivwbox.de" or a signature which is created from various information that is automatically transferred by your computer. IP addresses are not stored via this method and only processed in anonymized form. The audience measurement was developed in consideration of data protection. The goal of the audience measurement is to statistically determine user intensity and the number of users of a specific website. Individual users are not identified at any point in time. Their identity is always protected. They will not receive any advertizing via the system.  
For websites which are members of the IVW German Audit Bureau of Circulation (Informationsgemeinschaft zur Feststellung der Verbreitung von Werbeträgern e.V., [www.ivw.eu](http://www.ivw.eu/) or that participate in the study "Internet Facts", organized by the Work Group Online Research (Arbeitsgemeinschaft Online-Forschung e.V., [AGOF](http://www.agof.de/)), user statistics are published monthly by the AGOF and the AGMA (Arbeitsgemeinschaft Media-Analyse e.V., [ag.ma](http://www.agma-mmc.de/)), as well as the IVW and can be viewed at [http://www.agof.de](http://www.agof.de/), [http://www.agma-mmc.de](http://www.agma-mmc.de/) and [http://www.ivw.eu](http://www.ivw.eu/). In addition to the publication of measurement data, the IVW also regularly checks the SZM process to ensure that it is used in accordance with regulations and data protection. You can find additional information about the SZM process on the website of INFOonline GmbH ([https://www.infonline.de](https://www.infonline.de/)), the operators of the SZM process, as well as the data protection website of AGOF (<http://www.agof.de/datenschutz>) and the data protection website of IVW ([http://www.ivw.eu](http://www.ivw.eu/)). 

You can object to the data processing by the SZM under the following link: [http://optout.ivwbox.de](http://optout.ivwbox.de/).

**2\. Use of Google Analytics**

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses "cookies", which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. In case of the activation of IP anonymization on this website, your IP address will be shortened beforehand by Google in the space of the member states of the European Union or in other contractual states of the European Economic Area. In exceptional cases, the complete IP address is transmitted to a server of Google in the United States and shortened there. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above. You can prevent the storage of cookies by the corresponding settings of your browsing software. However, we point out that you may not be able to use the websites to their full extent in this case. Furthermore, you can prevent the logging of the data (including your IP address) referring to the usage of the website created by the cookie by Google as well as the processing of this data by Google by downloading and installing the add-on available under the following link: [The current link is <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en>.

3\. Usage of Services to Optimize Online Advertisements 

The company nugg ad AG has been charged to present advertisements based on the users' interests on behalf of upjers. In order to do this, data will be shared between nugg ad and upjers. If you visit our website, nugg ad will save a cookie on your hard drive. This cookie serves to save individual usage habits (visited web sites, amount of visits, times of visit, duration of stay on specific sites, etc.) on your hard drive. These usage profiles will be evaluated anonymously be nugg ad, to be able to present you products that actually meet your interests on our websites or other websites later on. No data such as name, address, email-address or IP-address is being saved during this process. For further info, please visit the company web page of nugg ad under: 

http://www.nugg.ad/en/company/privacy 

You may revoke the saving of cookies by nugg ad at any time. To do this, please just activate the "no" button in the "opt out" area of nugg ad's homepage under: 

http://www.nugg.ad/en/index 

http://www.nugg.ad 

Alternatively, you may disable the saving of these cookies by respective browser-settings also. 

**4\. Handling data when using integrated games**

Several upjers games are integrated on platforms of social networks (Facebook, above all). There, the games are labeled "Apps", or "Applications", respectively. If you want to use these games, you are prompted to authorize the collection/storage of the following data by Upjers:

* First name and surname, sex, date of birth
* Profile picture or corresponding URL
* Login e-mail address which was indicated upon the registration for Facebook
* Location and access devices
* User ID number, which is linked to publicly available information (on Facebook)
* User ID number to your friends, who are also connected with the game.

By clicking "Authorize", you acknowledge the collection, storage and processing of data in accordance with this data privacy statement.

Upjers points out that the scope of information obtained via Facebook can be influenced by privacy settings. Exertion of influence may particularly ensue by

* your controlling which information may be shared with/about you by your Facebook friends
* your blocking of particular applications, or preventing to collect specific information about you, respectively
* your ignoring particular game invitations
* your controlling who can see your activities

**4\. Play-now mode**

If upjers offers the possibility to use one or another game without the usual registration process, you receive a guest account. By using such a temporary guest account, the utilization of additional services for valuable consideration is not possible. You will not be prompted to depose personal data (such as your e-mail address). Instead, you are granted access to the game by using a guest name and a corresponding password. The guest name created in the guest account (that is assigned to you) will be deleted after a certain period of time after your registration. However, you may register for the game. The personal data obtained in the scope of the registration are dealt with as is indicated in this data privacy statement.

## § 5 Disclosure of personal data

Upon request, upjers will immediately inform you about all data stored about you. This information will be transmitted digitally, normally via e-mail, in principle. 

## § 6 Third-Party Websites / Links

This data privacy statement is not valid for third-party websites, including websites that users may reach via links on websites maintained by upjers. upjers cannot be made liable for how the providers of third-party websites handle the users' data. In particular, upjers cannot be made liable if such websites do not follow the same data privacy standards upjers offers its users. upjers therefore recommends that its users always carefully read the data privacy statements of linked sites.

## § 7 Changes of Data Privacy Statement

upjers reserves the right to change this data privacy statement at any time, but upjers will always adhere to the currently applicable data security laws. upjers advises its users to inform themselves on each visit to these websites and games about the current data privacy statement. In case upjers plans to use its users' personal data on a larger scale, upjers will notify users of any changes beforehand.

Valid as of June 2012

upjers GmbH & Co. KG  
Company registration number: HRA Bamberg 10694  
Address: Hafenstrasse 13, 96052 Bamberg, Germany  
Email: mail@upjers.com (no support)  
Telephone: Tel: +49-951/5109080 (no support)  
Tax number: 20717951108  
VAT number: DE251065630

General partner: upjers Verwaltungs GmbH  
Address: Hafenstrasse 13, 96052 Bamberg, Germany  
Company registration number: HRB Bamberg 5558  
CEO: Klaus Schmitt
